How have you been?
Can we talk?
Sure.
We should.
But before that…
-Fucking…
-Wait!
-Hear me out!
-You bastard!
They're at it again. Fucking hell.
What the fuck are the police doing,
letting people like that walk free?
Hurry up and eat, you bitch!
Aren't you going to work?
Always giving me shit. For fuck's sake.
Come here, you bastard!
Everyone out.
Get the fuck out, you bastards!
Wait.
Don't go.
It's gonna be a long night.
Luckily, I have plenty of time tonight.
You fucking piece of shit.
Fuck!
You're still alive?
Thought you came here with a death wish.
-Why aren't you dead yet?
-Your money.
You want it back, right?
Is my money still alive?
Find someone for me.
Then I'll give you your money back.
Look at this bastard.
Fine. Who should I find?
Me.
What the hell are you saying?
Please
find me.
I lost myself.
You fucking bastard.
Please…
Please find me.
MOUSETRAP
I sent all the money we agreed on.
We're done now, right?
Right, Moon-jae?
Hello?
Stay sharp until it's all wrapped up.
Just hang in there until then.
Okay. Don't worry.
Oh, but we…
So,
you got cleaned out
by a guy who looks exactly like you?
Your house, money, everything?
You expect me to believe that?
You bastard, if you were me,
would you just believe that?
I can't believe it either.
But it's true.
There's nothing left in my name.
That bastard even changed my ID number.
Officially, I'm not Je Moon-jae anymore.
I'm just an empty shell.
A person who doesn't exist, dead or alive.
I have to catch him.
The bastard who looks like me.
You're the only one
who can prove I'm Je Moon-jae.
And only you can help me.
Why the fuck would I help you?
I should be killing you, you asshole.
You need to find your money.
And I need to find my name.
I have more than enough money.
Money isn't the issue for me.
Okay? Life is.
I've gotten tired of it, you see.
All you need to do is write.
Give me the rights,
and I'll make it take off, film or TV.
-Okay?
-Okay.
If I'm lying, Noja,
beat me to death.
Why do you keep calling me Noja?
Am I your friend or something,
you bastard?
You told me to use your name.
Is this your place?
Here.
What's this?
I got one for you.
Go write something good.
I already have a laptop.
Just use this one.
We're in the same boat now.
Thank you, sir.
For God's sake.
"Sir"? Are we thugs or what?
Just call me Noja.
Okay, Noja.
Finding people?
Don't worry. I'm an expert.
But if you screw me over again,
you'll suffer a long, slow death.
You won't die easily.
I spent three fucking years
looking for this bastard.
Now I have to find another one
who looks exactly like him?
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
We must find someone else first.
Fucking hell.
Who is it now?
My friend who had me skim money off you.
It'll be faster to find him first.
They're in it together.
Jesus, how…
How the fuck did I get mixed up
with this bastard?
Listen carefully.
You're my hostage now.
If I find my money, you live.
If I don't, you fucking die. Got it?
Do everything you can to help me
if you want to live.
-Okay.
-Damn it!
Goddamn it.
Do you really have to go this far?
How am I supposed to sleep like this?
Can't you at least loosen it a bit?
PRIVATE DETECTIVE AGENCY
What?
He got caught already?
Huh?
Oh, he went there on his own.
This is getting interesting.
Excuse me?
We're not open yet. Lunch starts at noon.
Oh, I'm not here to eat.
You know Mr. Kim Yeong-geun, right?
Could you tell me where he is?
Sir?
Who even is that?
Huh?
I heard you used to work together.
Oh, come on.
Don't be like that.
If you know, just tell me.
Where are you from?
I'm with the police.
Jeez, don't bother the guy.
He's clean now.
God.
What, you think other people
don't live clean?
Just tell me where your "clean" guy is.
It's nothing serious.
It'll just take a minute.
I just need to see him for a moment.
What's this about?
I came because he didn't pay a fine.
A fine?
A summary summons. Why won't he take it?
The fine's not even 200,000 won.
If he keeps this up, his assets
could get seized over a 200,000-won fine.
I'm busy as hell already.
Have a good one!
PRIVATE DETECTIVE AGENCY
I'd be retired by now
if I'd put that money into real estate.
That no-good bastard.
How did I end up
getting mixed up with him?
To become a new man…
I was crazy to trust him.
If a thug becomes a businessman,
does that make him a new man?
That's basically identity fraud.
Don't push it.
Okay?
Because of you, I never became a new man.
I'm still the same old me, you bastard.
I'm a dangerous man. You hear me?
What is he blabbering about?
All right. Let's go.
To catch the bastard who stole
from the bastard who stole from me.
His address might be registered with
the accountants' association or something.
For lawyers and accountants,
associations are important.
Are you listening?
Yeah. I hear you!
But I've got a plan too, so just zip it.
Where are we going?
We're on our way
to meet the blog owner you found.
The one who posted the reunion photos.
That's how you got to the reunion, right?
You know where he is?
Know what's wrong with kids these days?
They put their personal info everywhere.
Blog, Instagram.
His personal info is everywhere.
These days, if you hack someone's phone,
you can clean them out in an instant.
Don't ever post stuff online.
Criminals and would-be criminals
shouldn't do that.
Got it?
BOARD-CERTIFIED PLASTIC SURGEON, MD
Wow, you must be pretty good with a knife.
You're basically creating faces
from scratch, huh?
This is straight-up identity fraud.
Isn't that illegal,
changing someone's face like that?
-Damn it.
-Huh?
Kyeong-tae. You really don't remember me?
It's me, Moon-jae. Je Moon-jae.
And you're…
You're Jeon Kyeong-tae.
Your last name, Jeon.
You really don't remember me?
What do you two think you're doing?
Seriously?
Then call the police.
What, you think I won't call the police?
What are you trying to--
How about some plastic surgery, Doc?
SON SOO-HYUN
The number you've dialed does not exist.
Please check and try again.
That bastard totally went off the grid.
This guy's not involved.
You can't go to crowded places.
You can't go to open spaces,
and you don't like tight spaces either.
You've got so many fucking issues.
Burgers taste best at the joint.
Sometimes you're fine,
sometimes you're not.
It's all because of your guilt, punk.
The guilt of running off with my money!
I need my meds.
I'm anxious. I never know
when the symptoms will flare up.
You said you need a prescription.
Why didn't you get that doctor
to write you one, you dumbass?
Soo-hyun always got them for me. Damn it.
Why are you looking at me?
Am I your errand boy, punk?
Did somebody say that?
Aren't we on the same team?
We're in the same boat!
You no-good bastard. Seriously.
Move aside.
Just take these and get by for now.
What's this?
One's a painkiller.
I don't know what the other one is.
I can't just take any meds.
You don't know the story
of Wonhyo and the skull water?
It's all about how you take it, punk!
Who's that bastard impersonating me?
Soo-hyun brought him to the reunion
about a year ago.
At first, we didn't recognize him,
but then he looked like the guy
in the graduation pic.
So we thought he was Moon-jae.
See? They're in this together.
But this doesn't make any sense.
I've had drinks with Moon-jae
so many times recently.
Turns out, he's a famous writer.
But
you don't even remember
what happened on our school trip.
That's not something you forget!
Moon-jae remembered it clearly.
You keep going on about some school trip.
What about it?
What happened? Let's hear it. What is it?
There was a fire.
All the students had to evacuate.
It was a total mess.
And you don't remember that?
Does that make sense?
You are Je Moon-jae, right?
And he got plastic surgery
just for the money?
Why? He could've just taken it all.
You said it was in that bastard's account.
Because it was Je Moon-jae's money.
And I'm not Je Moon-jae anymore.
Even if you go to the police,
you'd be a Je Moon-jae impersonator?
I guess so.
And he lured me with a card in your name
so I could find you, huh?
Because I'd kill you if I caught you.
I'd be doing his dirty work.
Then why did he warn me to run?
Why not just let you kill me?
Maybe the job's not done yet.
Maybe he hasn't moved all the money.
That could be it.
That's an interesting bastard.
You mean "bastards."
You little shit.
Where are we going now?
Hey, where are we going?
I told you. This is a waste of time.
I've been here before.
You only see what you know.
I mean…
You coming?
It's just…
Elevators are a bit…
What a load of bullshit.
Must be great exercise.
If you scratch someone's car,
any civilized person
would leave their number.
You accountants are all educated, right?
Am I wrong?
What's this country coming to?
Just a moment.
He doesn't work here anymore.
I'll check the parking log to…
Here it is. A white BMW. Is that correct?
-Yes, white.
-Okay.
-What's that bastard's plate number?
-The plate number is…
Hey, we're done here. See you downstairs.
No, that's not it.
Yeah, white. 5340.
Got it. Find out fast!
Did you find him?
ENTER AMOUNT
2,000,000 WON
Okay.
I asked if you found it.
Fuck, you've gotta wait.
For who?
None of your business.
It's a trade secret.
WHITE BMW 5340
1,500,000 WON REWARD
WHITE BMW 5340 WANTED
Money exchange, huh?
Shit, I screwed up.
I guess you can smoke in here.
Oh, that's great.
Oh, you can't?
What is this place?
What do you mean? It's just an office.
Why?
Oh, come on.
What kind of office has no computers?
Hi.
-Hey, babe.
-Yeah.
Hello.
Look.
I'm not interested
in your illegal escort stuff, okay?
Are you close with the guys upstairs?
-Why?
-I'm just interested.
I don't wanna get involved.
And you won't be.
Don't worry.
My life is already complicated enough.
I'm not lying.
I hear he finds people for a living.
Well, it's a private detective agency.
He's different.
He can even find unidentified people.
Even if you hide from your debts,
he'll track you down in no time.
You know those guys
who run online gambling sites?
-Yeah.
-They come around a lot.
They really went after someone yesterday.
But if they beat up people like that,
wouldn't they die?
They probably would.
Anyway,
don't let him know I said this.
He looks scary as hell.
I get scared
every time I see him in the hallway.
It must've been hard for you. Here.
PARK SUN-YONG
Let's keep in touch, okay?
Fuck. You said I wouldn't be involved.
I'm just interested.
Take care.
The fuck?
EVERYTHING WILL BE FINE, SO DON'T WORRY
IT'S ALMOST OVER, OKAY?
It's almost over.
5340?
SEOUL DELIVERY RIDERS ASSOCIATION
WHITE BMW 5340 WANTED
The Heart Sutra
has nothing to do with Noja.
Just listen and be grateful, damn it.
It's why you're still alive.
But why does this bastard look familiar?
Maybe it's because he looks so plain?
I'm surprised
he's still active on social media.
It's private now.
I downloaded this early this morning.
Early this morning?
You're diligent.
You gotta be more diligent
than the ones who ran off.
Nothing in life is easy. Okay?
Everything's tough and exhausting.
That's life.
So you were lazy chasing me, huh?
You hid out for three years.
How was I supposed to catch you,
you little shit?
Damn it.
Hello?
Yeah. Okay.
Send me the address.
What? They already found him?
But he's still in Seoul.
Why didn't he run?
If I were him, I'd have run by now.
You were right. He's still got loose ends.
Who are you?
You know me?
What is it?
RUN AWAY. RIGHT NOW.
Goddamn it.
Just stay here, punk!
Shit.
Damn it.
Fuck!
Hey, punk. You good?
God, you no-good bastard. Seriously.
You said that bastard
had a guy tailing me, right?
Yeah.
He was tailing me a couple of days ago.
I ran into him.
I should've roughed that bastard up more.
How was I supposed to know
that bastard was him?
He even ditched his car.
He must've been in a hurry.
So we wait here for him?
What if he doesn't come back?
But it's strange.
The timing is just too perfect.
Huh? How did he stay one step ahead of us?
There's not much there.
There's a lot here!
Look at the dates, you punk!
These are all from a few days ago!
He's had his dashcam off for days.
He knew someone would search the car
if things went south.
What do we do now?
You've got a plan B, right?
You said you're an expert
at finding people.
-That'll be 70,000 won.
-Right.
That'll be 2,000,000 today.
Gas, food, my time, and all that.
You'll be charged for all this.
You know that, right?
If a client hires a private detective,
they should pay up.
Client? You said I'm your hostage.
You're both.
Where to?
What's it to you?
I don't care if I'm a hostage or a client.
Just tell me where we're going!
We're going with plan B, you punk.
Happy now?
Those who run can hide themselves,
but they can't hide their families.
Why?
Even within a family,
each person has their own life.
How did you know Soo-hyun's kid goes here?
Instagram.
That damn Instagram.
-Where to?
-Aren't we here for his address?
You think they'll just tell you?
They don't know you.
You really don't know
how the world works, do you?
Close the door!
Open that.
Give me one. Hurry.
What's all this?
This one's way too far.
Give me a closer one. One in Seoul.
Seoul. Right.
SEOUL MAPO POLICE STATION
Stay here.
Why?
Just stay here, punk!
Ever seen a detective in sweats?
Da-eun hasn't been in for a few days.
So I called her mother,
and she said Da-eun's taking a break.
Seems like it's a family matter.
What kind of family matter?
I'm not sure.
She just said
Da-eun's taking a break for a while.
I guess I'll have to go to this address
and ask myself.
What's this about?
Da-eun's parents aren't the kind
to commit a crime.
It's always the ones you least suspect
who do it.
All right. Thank you for your cooperation.
Crap.
We're with the police.
Well. We're with the police.
What's wrong with him?
-What's going on?
-What?
Why are the police here?
What? Hey!
Slow down!
What's wrong? Someone's there!
What the hell is going on here?
-Hey, did you see something?
-No.
Jeez.
Move, damn it.
Goddamn it.
It's so quiet.
The cops even went to the daycare.
No way they are home.
Cops! Get down!
-Cops! Get the hell down.
-Cops?
They're gone.
I didn't even report him.
Why did the police come for Soo-hyun?
Yeah.
What the hell has he been up to?
You should've picked better friends,
you dumbass!
Could be the car you smashed.
Why would they go after his daughter
over that? You idiot!
For fuck's sake.
We need to reach him before the police do.
Otherwise, fuck,
the money goes to the government.
Don't worry. It'll be fine.
Once everything's done,
why don't we take a trip?
You said you wanted to take a break.
And we should let Da-eun see the world
before she starts school.
The police?
I told you we just have to be patient
a bit longer.
We were almost there.
Why couldn't you wait a few more days?!
Why? Damn it!
Shit.
All day,
all we had was a burger.
I'm kinda hungry.
Come on. Let's eat something.
Are you buying?
I've got no money.
Soo-hyun even blocked mobile payments.
How did he get his hands on your phone?
He bought me this phone.
That was a stupid question.
Give it to me.
Give it!
Huh? Hey! Why?
No wonder his timing was perfect.
He planted something on your phone,
you dumbass!
He knew we were onto him!
God, you stupid dumbass.
Seriously! Goddamn it!
Damn it.
Still, you should've--
What is it?
Hey, go pick it up.
It's over there.
That fucking scared me.
Why the hell does he keep calling me?
It's so annoying.
Yes, sir.
Where are you?
You told me to follow up on the tip.
You said it was a prank.
Yes, I did.
But something's bothering me.
You slacking off?
What the fuck do you mean? Seriously.
Don't we have work to do?
Everyone's working their asses off,
and you haven't shown up all day!
-I mean--
-Hey.
Just file the report as is and wrap it up.
But I should at least meet that thug.
How the fuck am I supposed
to write this report or whatever?
Then did you at least find the bastard?
ESCORT LADY
HE JUST CAME IN
I found him. Yes. I just fucking did!
I just found him!
I'll file the report and close it out.
This is fucking bullshit.
Huh?
Just eat it already.
Elders first.
You bastard.
Hey, hurry up and eat.
We have to head out.
We're going out again?
-Where to?
-Somewhere.
From now on,
don't ever tell me where we're going.
Never ever tell me.
If you do, I'll just--
Fishing.
Eat up.
I'm done.
Did you get rid of the one at the morgue?
No, not yet.
Hurry up and burn it.
Yes, sir.
PRIVATE DETECTIVE AGENCY
She said he was here. Damn it.
The light's off. That lady…
Who the hell is that?
It's that bastard from yesterday.
The one Noja beat the crap out of.
So many new faces.
That means things are fucked.
Don't know him, huh?
They were tearing into each other,
and now they're friends?
These bastards are just unbelievable.
But how do you know he'll come?
That bastard's very interested in you.
What you're doing and where you're going.
He's tracking you all day on his phone.
He's going to come check.
Your dead body.
GWANGNAM RESERVOIR
Give me a tissue.
Don't get too close, man.
Yes, sir.
This might take a while,
so lie down and get comfortable.
It's a good place to bury a body.
You're dangerous, huh?
Must've buried a lot of bodies.
Would they even care?
Wouldn't it be better for them if I died?
If their goal was to kill you,
you'd be dead already.
Since you can't die yet,
they'll come here to check on you.
That's the point of this fishing trip.
Hey, Soo-hyun. It's me, Moon-jae.
Can you talk for a moment?
I need you to check something for me.
Just in case.
Got a bite.
Subtitle translation by: Sung In Jang